p1=[
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"bol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"čov","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ca","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ht","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"to","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"tovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"medv","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sec","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sečno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"lja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"gov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"zin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"oc","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"omil","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ovd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šice","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"podr","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"poned","osnova2":"ljak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"ćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"dnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"predavan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"voz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"prol","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"niti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"razum","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"tko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"čanj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ćati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"titi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ver","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"deći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"svin","osnova2":"tina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ž","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"šted","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"šut","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"stenina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"ul","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"uv","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vid","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rojatno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"tar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"vol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"zaljubl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije",""],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zda","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je",""],"osnova":"živ","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
]
p2=[
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arapa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aša","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"okolada","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ovjek","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uvati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"evapčić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ćevapči","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"kovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"druga","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"hla","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kau","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"kola","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ljubi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nao","osnova2":"ale","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nau","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"nave","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obi","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"ekivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"papu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"rje","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sendvi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sije","osnova2":"anj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"simpati","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"sveu","osnova2":"ilište","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"tr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"era","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"erati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"velja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"cvije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č",""],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"drve","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"du","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ga","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ispe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"iza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"kafi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"liš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"odje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"oti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"posje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"povr","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"prolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sino","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sljede","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"sre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"še","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"uop","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć",""],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
]

p3=[{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"em","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ep","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ez","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"patli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž",""],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"ama","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"dovi","osnova2":"enja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"","osnova2":"umbir","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"grož","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"izme","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"iznena","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"endan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"svi","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ",""],"osnova":"tako","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
]